10/31/2019 (1) Resume

Lisa Eisler, MD Anesthesiology, New York, NY (516) 835-8787 · lisa.eisler2@gmail.com

Summary

Dr. Lisa Eisler is an anesthesiologist in New York, NY and is affiliated with New York-Presbyterian Hospital. She received her medical degree from Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine and has been in practice 5 years. She specializes in pediatric anesthesiology.

Experience

Trustees Of Columbia University In The City Of New York · New York, NY December 2018 - Present

Anesthesiology Services Of CPMC · New York, NY September 2018 - Present

Affiliations

New York-Presbyterian Hospital Current Affiliation New York, NY

Education & Training

New York Presbyterian Hospital - Columbia Campus

Residency, Anesthesiology, 2012 - 2016

Harvard University No Degree, Premedical, 2006 - 2007 Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine Class of 2012

Harvard University B.A., Psychology, Magna Cum Laude, 2002 - 2006

Certification & Licensure

NY State Medical License 2017 - 2021

American Board of Anesthesiology Pediatric Anesthesiology

American Board of Anesthesiology Anesthesiology 10/31/2019 (1) Resume

Awards, Honors & Recognition

Honorable Mention, Resident Research Competition New York State Society of Anesthesiologists, 2018

Clinical Research Training Program Fellowship Sidney Kimmel Cancer Center/Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, 2009 Best Clinical Research Abstract-Academic Evening Columbia University Department of Anesthesiology, 2017

Profile in the Harvard Science Review Harvard College, 2005